End the curse.
Fear Street: 1666 is a mystery, horror film directed by Leigh Janiak.
In 1666, a colonial town is gripped by a hysterical witch-hunt that has deadly consequences for centuries to come,
and it's up to teenagers in 1994 to finally put an end to their town's curse, before it's too late.
Sarah Fier / Deena, played by Kiana Madeira.
Henry / Josh, played by Benjamin Flores Jr..
Hannah Miller / Samantha Fraser, played by Olivia Scott Welch.
Solomon Goode / Nick Goode, played by Ashley Zukerman.
Martin, played by Darrell Britt-Gibson.
'Real' Sarah Fier, played by Elizabeth Scopel.
Fear Street Part Three: 1666 (titled onscreen as Fear Street 1666 for its first half and Fear Street 1994: Part 2 for its second half) is a 2021
American supernatural period horror film directed by Leigh Janiak, who co-wrote the screenplay with Phil Graziadei and Kate Trefry.
Based on the book series of the same name by R.
Stine, it is the third installment of the Fear Street trilogy after Part One: 1994 and Part Two: 1978, and stars Kiana
Madeira, Ashley Zukerman, Gillian Jacobs, Olivia Scott Welch, Benjamin Flores Jr., and Darrell Britt-Gibson.
The film follows the origins of Shadyside's curse in the mid-17th century
and the survivors in 1994 who try to put an end to it.
Produced by Chernin Entertainment, a film adaptation of Fear Street began
development at 20th Century Fox in 2015, with Janiak hired in 2017.
Filming for the trilogy took place back-to-back from March to September 2019 in
Georgia, with the intention of a theatrical release in June 2020.
However, due to the COVID-19 pandemic and the acquisition of 21st Century Fox by Disney, Chernin Entertainment
ended their distribution deal with 20th Century Studios and sold rights to Netflix in August 2020.
Fear Street Part Three: 1666 premiered at the Los Angeles State Historic Park
on July 14, 2021, and was released by Netflix on July 16, 2021.
It received generally positive reviews from critics.
A fourth film, Fear Street: Prom Queen, was released on May 23, 2025.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
curse, teenage girl, witchcraft, witch hunt.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.